Sir, we're here for the boxing class.
Precious?
Brandon?
It's really nice to meet you.
Do you think he's fit to be
a father figure to me?
Are you still looking for a father?
Of course!
Mr. and Mrs. Chan-Li were very responsive.
We just need to give them
something worth their investment.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- And we need to focus.
[CHARM] Didn't you tell Yani
you can't go to his exhibit?
[TONI] I said I'd be there later.
[MARIELA] It's Saturday.
Where are you going?
[ABI] My boss is asking me
to come to work.
Like I told you, Ma, I'll be like Abi.
I'm almost there.
Just wait.
[BILLY] She said she owns
an internet cafe.
- [JORDAN] She could be lying.
- How's it going?
- Did you find it?
- Yes, but it's closed now.
It's closed only because
she has debts to the landlady.
The landlady said Abi's going to pay.
She won't take anything back.
Hey! Hey, those computers are mine!
Those are my computers!
[TONI] We didn't just get her computers.
- Ta-da!
- These, too!
[BILLY] Auntie Pres, this is really mine.
She even pretended
to be your fan just to rob you!
[BILLY] Just let her try doing that again.
I'm not going to back down.
[BOTTLE THUDS]
I'll get back at Billy.
That witch.
Relax.
We'll get even with her. Don't worry.
Come on, 'Bi. Check this out.
- [BOTTLE THUDS]
- 'Bi.
Hey, what are you doing?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What did you do, Caloy?
What's that?
'Bi, I love you this much.
- [CALOY EXHALES]
- [SIGHS]
'Bi, you're always by my side.
Everyone else has left me.
I'm all alone.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
But from now on…
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
…it's going to be you and me forever, 'Bi.
You are permanently etched onto my heart.
I love you.
- [SOFT BLOW LANDS]
- Ouch…
[GROANS]
This is a fresh one!
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
Hey, you're smiling.
You can't shake the butterflies, huh?
[CHUCKLES DRYLY]
Let me see that smile.
What do you want?
Want me to get your shoes back? Huh?
I'll take care of it.
I'll go there right now!
Get my computers too while you're at it.
If only Ms. Tere hadn't
sold them to Billy.
Damn it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
W-Wait a minute. Where did they take them?
They said they'll donate them.
[CALOY SUCKS TEETH]
B-But where are they giving them away?
We need them!
Not anymore. Forget it.
She can have them.
I don't need them anymore.
[HUFFS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I have other plans for Billy.
[MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
[SNICKERS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROBBIE] Go, wash them.
[GLASSES CLINKING IN DISTANCE]
I'LL HOLD YOUR HAND IN THE MADNESS
- No more orders coming in?
- [HUMMING]
- [TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WOMAN CRYING]
- [FRIEND 1] Cheers, girls.
- [FRIEND 2] Let's dance!
[BOTTLES CLINK]
- [SINGS] Just lean…
- [FRIEND 3] Here's to her!
- [FRIEND 4] Come on!
- [FRIEND 5] Well?
[HEELS CLACK]
[WOMAN CRYING]
[FRIEND 1] Let's do it!
- [FRIEND 2] Smile!
- Just lean on me
[HUMMING]
[TENDER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's just dance To the beat of our hearts
- [SQUEALS] A perfect match!
- You naughty kid!
Why haven't you bathed yet?
You're already stinky.
[SNIFFS] Go take a bath!
Billy, check it out. Auntie's blushing.
Look at her!
- Right?
- Oh my!
When was this?
- The other day.
- [PRECIOUS] Oh, wow!
- [OLIVER YELPS]
- Teasing me, huh?
You scared me! [EXHALES]
- Auntie Pres…
- Yeah?
- You're all smiles here.
- So giddy!
Oh, please!
- Your smile's so beautiful!
- He should court you now.
It'll be fun.
Wow! [CHUCKLES]
I've never seen you smile
like this before.
- Can I see it?
- Show us, show us.
- It's not like that.
- It is!
- It isn't.
- Do it properly.
That was it.
- Show us, show us!
- Who's this?
- That man you're with.
- [OLIVER] That's Sir Eric.
He was in the same restaurant
where we had lunch.
- Mm!
- I joined him instead…
so I wouldn't disturb Auntie!
- Shush! You're so naughty!
- Ow, ow!
- You might've disturbed him.
- Not really.
- How was he, Auntie Pres?
- Okay. Sir Eric's kind.
- No, I meant Brandon.
- Huh?
Your date.
- Was there a spark?
- There was!
- Huge! Like electricity!
- Oh, really?
- There was a spark!
- Is that so?
- You saw it?
- There was no spark!
- [BILLY] There's none?
- [OLIVER] Pillow fight!
- [BILLY SHRIEKING HAPPILY]
- [PRECIOUS] Come here!
[OLIVER] Pillow fight! Pillow fight!
- [PRECIOUS] Oliver, that hurts!
- Ahh!
Ah! No, sorry, sorry. No. Auntie Pres!
- Ahh! Ahh!
- [BILLY] Auntie Pres!
- There was a spark!
- You're giddy!
[PRECIOUS] Wait, wait! Let's take a break!
Wait, wait, wait!
[OLIVER CHUCKLES]
- I'm tired.
- There's a spark!
- That was a different smile.
- There's a spark?
- No!
- Mm-hmm.
- It was a giddy smile.
- It was different.
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Oliver? Hm, here's your lunch, okay?
Finish it. Sometimes,
you don't eat your fruit.
- Okay, Billy.
- All right.
You ready?
- Ready!
- [BILLY CLAPS]
Ready. Okay.
In your science module about life cycle,
what does the stage
called "fledging" mean?
"Fledging." Fledging is the stage
where young birds leave their nest
to learn how to fly.
Oh! Very good!
Congratulations!
You win one million pesos!
Very good!
Just one million?
It should be five million!
- I studied hard, you know.
- It can't be five million!
It should actually be 10 million
because I memorized that.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry I wasn't there
for your first boxing class.
I'll make it up to you
next week, I promise.
Billy, I understand you're busy.
And I should get used to that.
What?
What if I get accepted
into the University of Kingsley?
Just you wait, Billy.
When I become a successful
software engineer,
I will take care of you.
Is that so?
Okay! You have to take care of me, okay?
But
right now, I just want you to have fun,
to achieve all your dreams,
and to do whatever you want.
I will take care of you.
My dream?
I also dream of going to America
to visit Papa's grave.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay.
- Next? Okay.
- Yes. Next question.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHING]
- [PHONE THUDS]
[GATE CREAKS OPEN]
Eric.
What's this? [HUFFS]
I trusted you.
I let you rent this apartment.
But, apparently, you faked
your police clearance?
This is the original!
You have a hit!
I called NLEA. They said
you were imprisoned in Canada.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I really need a job.
You'll have to look elsewhere.
You're fired!
Get out!
I can't lose my spot in the canteen!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am…
I need to make it up to my kids.
But this is Oliver.
Ms. Billy, here is the list
of our employees
whose contracts are expiring next month.
Blaire's one of them.
If we're looking for ways to save,
to cut some losses, we can downsize.
And since these employees'
contracts are ending,
we technically have no commitment to them.
Agatha, I have a commitment to them.
They're the people behind our success.
And now that the company
is facing challenges,
is it right for them to be casualties
just to cut our losses?
No.
It's just a bit impractical, Ms. Billy.
We will renew all of their contracts.
Okay, Ms. Billy.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Agatha.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You need this.
I missed this.
Thank you.
You make it look so easy.
Being strong.
Confident.
Composed.
You're such a sweet-talker.
You need something, don't you?
- I don't.
- Hmm…
I'm just telling the truth.
I could say the same to you.
We got this.
We do.
By the way, how's Grandpa Jude?
He's okay.
Here.
Oh no!
Is he all right?
They didn't find anything in the X-ray.
- Sure?
- He's okay.
Okay, good.
They're becoming negligent.
That's why I'm looking
for a better facility.
So meaning,
somewhere more expensive.
Mm. Come on, we'll share.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[JORDAN] Cheers.
- Mm.
- See?
Chief?
We're ready.
Okay.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I know we made the right decision
choosing you.
We are so excited for this collaboration.
Well, I'm just so, so grateful
I did not take the bait!
Yes, because the original idea
came from the newest member
of the Pebblng family,
and not from that Billy.
Well, she's a gem, for sure,
so don't let her get away.
Oh, ma'am, thank you so much.
And with that, cheers! Cheers!
- Cheers! Cheers!
Sir, cheers!
Morrie! Congratulations to us!
[WINE GLASSES CLINK]
I love to travel, so…
What if a destination wedding?
Like, a wedding in Siargao
if the couple are surfers.
That's a good idea,
but we have to think of the budget.
Of course, it'll be a destination wedding,
so we can't fly all the guests, unless…
we have sponsors.
Or…
we can make it into a fashion event!
What if we brand our wedding events?
I mean, the famous event.
Let's have famous designers,
event stylists,
and caterers on board.
Okay. That's something we can explore.
Toni?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah! I love cruises.
But Yani was born
in the Year of the Tiger,
so he has a high risk
of injuries and accidents this year.
He's asked to be careful when traveling
or when doing anything near water.
- What?
- Huh?
A wedding on a cruise ship.
Ahh…
- Ah…
- Oh, okay.
How's your eye?
I'm okay, chief!
Look, it's basically gone now.
Girls,
thank you
for going the extra mile for this.
I'm sorry we got to a point
where someone got hurt.
[TONI] We all believe in LoveList.
I'm okay.
That Abi's just so irritating.
If she hadn't stolen LoveFeast,
then we would've been launching it today.
There is nothing we can do.
What won't change is we're getting closer
to our meeting with the investors,
so we have no choice but to
come up with a solid plan today.
Um, I think it's too late for that.
- [TONI] Why?
- [VALERIE] Look.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
Our would-be investors.
Huh…
That list! That was on my laptop!
Chief, you had me make a company profile
for each investor, remember?
Okay, that's enough!
- We have pizza!
- Have a break first.
Pizza break!
- [RALPH] Take a break first.
- [JORDAN] Pizza?
[MOUTHS] Thank you.
Dude.
Got any ideas?
Hmm!
What if you do the opposite of LoveFeast?
FeastLove?
No.
Instead of helping couples, you know,
to get married, to get together,
and stuff, but…
Help couples break up, I guess?
The-- The toxic ones.
- Hm, babe.
- Hm.
Babe, we're LoveList.
Your suggestion's bad.
- The boss won't approve that.
- Come on, Ralph.
I'm sure you know how stressful it can be
to save a business.
Don't you have any more ideas?
Or you don't know anything
'cause you're a rich kid.
Hey! It's good that my boyfriend
is very supportive,
even though he isn't part of our business.
Mmm!
I'm jelly.
Chief.
Even if we come up with a concept,
who are we gonna present the pitch to?
They already stole our potential
investors too.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[RALPH] Hm? All right!
The gang's all here.
Can we talk?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, Ms. Lucy!
Oh, Oliver!
Is Sir Eric here?
- Hey, Oliver.
- Hello, Sir Eric!
I have already written an essay
for my application
to the University of Kingsley.
Is it all right if you give it a read?
I don't want to bother my sister with it.
As for Auntie, she said it's good.
Sir, maybe you could give me
some suggestions?
All right. I'll go over it later.
Thank you!
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
Eric.
[SIGHS]
I hope I don't lose my business
because of this.
I'll be careful, ma'am.
Why don't you just tell
your child the truth?
I tried to.
But my eldest doesn't want
to listen to me.
I also think that if I want
to make it up to them,
and for them to forgive me,
I shouldn't use it,
not in that way.
For now… [EXHALES DEEPLY]
…my youngest and I
are doing just fine.
My eldest and I will be
on good terms soon.
How?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
But this isn't right!
It's better if you just quit
already, Toni!
Let's just stop this!
[TONI SCOFFS]
You want me to resign
just when our marriage
is right around the corner?
Are you serious?
And it's because you don't
spend time with me.
Who's more important? Me or your job?
Toni?
Yani?
Is everything okay?
Good thing you're here, Billy.
Join our conversation.
You're a part of our relationship anyway.
Isn't that right?
You're prioritizing this job over me.
Yani, it's not like that.
She's doing this for you.
She's doing this for the
future of the two--
No, she's doing this for you.
That's why she got hurt.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yani, I'm sorry she got hurt.
She was just trying to help so that--
So that you could settle your score.
It was for the company.
That the three of us worked so hard for.
That is now also helping
a lot of employees.
- Billy, she doesn't need LoveList.
- Hold up.
If not for LoveList,
the two of you wouldn't have met.
I can provide for her!
I just need her to trust me a little.
Yani, this isn't about
the ability to provide.
It's about purpose.
And Toni found that purpose
here at LoveList.
Now we're talking about purpose?
All right, then!
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Toni, make a choice.
Your purpose or me?
Love, don't do this to me--
No, no. Make a choice.
Toni, your purpose or me?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOMBER ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Toni…
["MAG-ISA LANG AKO"
BY SHANIAH ROLLO PLAYING]
["MAG-ISA LANG AKO" CONTINUES]
There are many kinds of love.
♪ Baby, I won't be long ♪
Heart-pounding.
This love song is really good.
It's not finished yet. And it's not a
love song. It's a friendship song.
Hmm…
There's also longing.
Thanks again for volunteering.
Anytime. It's for them.
And love full sacrifices.
I'm Melissa.
I'm having second thoughts
about my wedding.
My dad doesn't approve of him.
We celebrate the unique love story
behind each one.
How do we fund that?
[CAMILLE] We have to think
about the entire event.
Abi, ideas, please.
Uh, ideas…
- What are you doing here?!
- So what's the update on your computers?
You just won't let it go.
Why do you even care about the computers?
One of the computers
has our pictures and videos on it.
Find that computer, okay?
Every single picture and video
on it has to be deleted!
You know no one can ever find out
that we're connected!